<simulation-configuration>
	<name>Scenario - Module C - A=1,LOD=0.4</name>
    <category>business</category>   
    <behavior>com.github.kreatures.core.def.DefaultBehavior</behavior>
	<description>
	In this scenario the CEO Alice representing Antronic wants to acquire the company
	Brenton. Therefore she has to make a suitable offer to Bob the CEO of Brenton. To make a
	suitable offer Alice has to gather information. There are three pieces of information in
	the scenario: capital and investors (cai), receivables and payables (rap) and the order 
	situation (os). To make a suitable offer Alice has to know either cai and rap or cai and os.
	If she knows all three pieces of information she can make the optimal offer, that is the offer
	that is as low as possible and will be accepted. During the information gathering Alices has
	to be cautious because her information sources: claire and the detective will inform Bob if
	they learn about the acquisition because Bob offers a millon dollars to everbody who informs
	him about an acquisition. Claire and the Detective conclude that Alice wants to acquire
	the company if they learn that Alice wants to know about either the cai and rap or the cai
	and os, that means she has to asks one of them for the cai and the other for both of the
	other pieces of information.
	</description>

    <agent-instance>
		<name>alice</name>
        <agent-config source="config/agents/knowhow_agent_graphCA1.xml" />         
        <beliefbase-config source="config/beliefbases/asp_beliefbase.xml" />
         
        <capability>Query</capability>
        <capability>QueryAnswer</capability>
		<capability>Inform</capability>
		
        <desire>meet_bob</desire>
        <desire>acquire_brenton</desire>
        
        <data key="Confidential">
            (bob, __DEFAULT__, want_acquire)
            (claire, __DEFAULT__, want_acquire)
            (detective, __DEFAULT__, want_acquire)
        </data>
		<data key="KnowHow">
			meet_bob, golfing, 
			acquire_brenton, s_Query(a_bob, q_offer(N)), informed
		</data>
		<data key="situationFiles">
			golf_situation.xml, InvestigationSituation
		</data>
	</agent-instance>
      
	<agent-instance>
      	<name>bob</name>
      	
        <agent-config source="config/agents/knowhow_agent_graph.xml" />         
        <beliefbase-config source="config/beliefbases/asp_beliefbase.xml" />
         
      	<capability>QueryAnswer</capability>
        
        <data key="KnowHow">
			answer_query, s_QueryAnswer(p_honest),
		</data> 
	</agent-instance>
</simulation-configuration>
